nvidia.com 2019-06-17

# NVIDIA PRIVACY POLICY

**Effective 25 May 2018**

We promise to protect your privacy and your data. We never sell your data. We collect and use your data only if you give us permission.

You have the following rights:   

  * **Right to access.** You can see what data we have collected whenever you want.
  * **Right to take your data.** The data is yours. You can copy or move it whenever you want.
  * **Right to erasure.** We'll erase your personal data whenever you say the word. And even if you don't ask us to delete the data, we'll keep it only so long as it helps us serve you.
  * **Right to restrict use.** If you want us to stop using your data, we'll stop.
  * **Right to lodge a complaint.** We will protect your privacy and we will honor your choices. And if you feel we've failed in any way, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a data protection authority in your region.

### TYPES OF DATA WE MAY NEED

We will only ask for data that help our products delight you. We'll only ask for the minimum data we need, depending on the products and services you use. If you don't want to share your data, some of our products may not work, or work as well. Here is some information we might request:

  * Your contact information, including name, email address, phone number, and shipping address, so that we can contact you or ship items you have requested;
  * Your birthdate so we can verify age;
  * Your geographic region, including the city and state/province in which you reside, so we can comply with local laws;
  * Your device and network configuration, software for gaming and usage, and system performance so we can optimize your gaming hardware and software.

_Additional data collection can help us improve our products for gamers everywhere._  To help us provide the very best experiences for you and gamers everywhere, we'd like to collect some additional information about your gaming system and its performance. But we won't collect anything unless you tell us it's okay. This additional data includes:

  * Your device or network's technical information so we can find problems with certain devices and configurations;
  * Your error data so we can learn about the errors and fix them;
  * Your crash data so we can find and fix bugs.

We may analyze the data we've collected based on our interests in business forecasting and new product development. And, if you consent, we may use this data to identify certain audiences, including you, to receive games, apps, rewards, or relevant advertising.

### NVIDIA PRODUCTS AND SERVICES

If you want to know what kinds of data are collected by specific NVIDIA products and services, please visit [privacy.nvidia.com.](https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/privacy-center/)  

### OUR NVIDIA WEBSITES

If you visit any of our NVIDIA-branded websites, we or our third-party partners may collect information using cookies, web beacons, or log file information. Please see our [Cookies Policy](https://www.nvidia.co.uk/object/cookie-policy-uk.html) for more details. Here is some information we might collect:

  * Browser type, device type, URL addresses, IP addresses, or operating system type to improve our website, prevent fraudulent activity, understand how visitors use our website, and provide personalized content;
  * Geolocation data to understand where visitors reside, and to provide content especially for your location;
  * cookie data to personalize our webpage or serve relevant advertising.

### ENTERPRISE RELATIONSHIPS

If you do business with us, or if you sign up for our business literature, newsletters, conferences, or webinars, we may obtain or supplement your data with information from third parties such as your company name or job title. We may use this information to show you personalized website content. We may also share your contact information with an NVIDIA representative or business partner so they can communicate with you about NVIDIA-branded products or services.  

### THE WAY WE STORE AND TRANSFER DATA

We’ll transfer and keep your data in secure servers in the USA, where we are located. We are the data controller, and we’ll comply with the EU-U.S. and the Swiss-Privacy Shield framework, subject to enforcement by the Federal Trade Commission. This means we have certified that we adhere to the Privacy Principles of notice, choice, and accountability for onward transfer, security, data integrity, purpose limitation, access, recourse, enforcement, and liability. We remain responsible for any of your personal information that is shared with third parties for processing on our behalf. 

NVIDIA has committed to cooperate with the panel established by the EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner (FDPIC) with regard to unresolved Privacy Shield complaints concerning data transferred from the EU and Switzerland. Under certain conditions, you may invoke binding arbitration to resolve any complaint. We are subject to U.S. law, and we may be required to share data with U.S. law enforcement agencies. To learn more about Privacy Shield, please visit the U.S. Department of Commerce Privacy Shield website: [https://www.privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/). For more information regarding our Privacy Shield certification, please see: <https://www.privacyshield.gov/list>.

### KIDS PRIVACY POLICY

We take special care to protect the privacy of children who use our products and services. The NVIDIA [Kids Privacy Policy](https://www.nvidia.com/object/privacy_policy_children.html) contains more details.  

### CONTACT US

If you have any questions about NVIDIA's Privacy Policy or Kids Privacy Policy, please send an email to our Data Privacy Officer at [privacy@nvidia.com](mailto:privacy@nvidia.com).

You can also write to us at:

ATTN: Data Privacy Officer  
NVIDIA Corporation  
2788 San Tomas Expressway  
Santa Clara, CA 95051.

Updates to this policy will be posted at [privacy.nvidia.com](https://privacy.nvidia.com/).

## YOU CAN CHANGE YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS AT ANY TIME
